These Foreign-only subtitles ver. 2024-10 were created by ZoowlCZ.
ⓘ Very special thanks to Gwaith-i-Phethdain, Magpie of A Magpie's Nest and Friends, and Monoverantus
for their extraordinary work on deciphering the dialogs and lyrics.
ⓘ Special thanks also to TheGloriousLori and José Figueredo.
ⓘ For correct displaying of these subtitles, use a media player
supporting ASS tags in .srt files.
[Rohirric] Westu Aragorn hál.
[English] Be-thou Aragorn well!
[Sindarin] Ada.
[English] Father.
[Sindarin] Ada...
[English] Father...
[Sindarin] Ónen i-Estel Edain.
[English] I gave hope to Men.
[Sindarin] Ú-chebin...
[English] I have kept...
[Sindarin] ...Estel anim.
[English] ...no hope for me.
[Black Speech]  Katmuda!
[English]  Death to men!
[Black Speech]  Gorosh!
[English]  Louder!
[Black Speech]  Katmuda!
[English]  Death to men!
[Black Speech]  Gorosh!
[English]  Louder!
[Black Speech]  Katmuda!
[English]  Death to men!
[Black Speech]  Gorosh chadar!
[English]  Loud enough!